ELIJAH HOBZAR

Senior Web3 Frontend Engineer

@ elijahhobzar011@gmail.com

Kuantan, Malaysia

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

06/2017 - 02/2020 •

FrontEnd Developer

Location

Atos

- · Responsible for the quality of the user experience by developing tests suites that maintain functionality, performance and user flows across all modern browsers.
- Developed 10+ cluster projects and utilized public cloud, computing infrastructure services
 Designed 20+ front-end Web Interface for engineers and test- ops to control and monitor the onboard system using Angular2
- · Translated designs and wireframes into high quality code
- · Analyzed and optimized performance bottlenecks in 8+ existing backend systems, such as database queries and storage solutions, to increase responsiveness

03/2021 - 08/2021

Blockchain Developer

Location

Data Gen

- · Designed architecture of Data Gen eco-system on online RPG game market.
- · Development of a project governance token and get audited by Certik.
- · Initiated ideas for extending project to multi-chain

04/2020 - 04/2022

Sr.Frontend Developer

Location

Bitorix

- · Increased daily traffic from 45% to 80% in E-commerce platforms by redesigning existing websites to improve user experience and incorporated SEO
- · Designed and developed interfaces of Blockchain Web app that simplify dense information streams and solicit user interactions with machine learning feedback systems that feel intuitive and familiar
- · Developed app integration with REST and other APIs for Google Maps, social media logins, payment processors, and other services
- Collaborated with 2 different development teams on 4 new project designs and feature improvements
- Suggested 20+ improvements to product design and functionality as informed by user-experience reporting
- · Architected, implemented, and maintained 5 performant and scalable data-processing back-end system

07/2022 - 11/2023

Senior Web3 FrontEnd Engineer

Location

Web iSoft

- · Increased customer rating and satisfaction from 30% to 60% by implementing new ideas in smart contracts for NFT minting with solidity
- · Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams and used various Web APIs such as HTTP, REST and JSON to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates by 25%
- Created a system consist of swap, pool, staking, lending and borrowing contracts using solidity which improved the company income to 130%
- · Implemented 3rd-party integrations, such as payment and authentication systems
- · Built and maintained strategic relationships with potential investors and business partners and brainstormed new ideas
- Collaborated with colleagues from other teams to participate in the creation and testing of new software applications Increased 24% faster loading time and time spam per visit by +70 seconds in 5+ projects
- · Planned, wrote, and debugged web applications and software with complete accuracy

EDUCATION

09/2012 - 08/2016

Bachelor of Computer in Science University of London

SUMMARY

Senior engineer with 8+ years of professional experience in IT industry. Deep understanding of basic software infrastructure and agile development process with solid skills in web, mobile, and blockchain. Agile development, team collaboration, solution resolving and dedicated contribution are all my strengths and always working in a creative manner while improving self qualities and expertise.

LANGUAGES

Malay	English	
Proficient	Intermediate	

SKILLS

Agile	angular2	Apache	API apis	Blockchair	bootst	rap Clu	ster con	tentful CSS
Ethereu	m ethers	.js Fireba	ise Front-	end Git	Github	Golang	Google Ma	ps GraphQL
html5	Javascript	Jest J	Query Jso	n Laravel	Linux	Machine	Learning	Mocha
mongo	MongoDB	MySQL	Next.js	node nod	le.js PHF	react.	js Redux	rest
rest api	restful							